ace-learning.com.sg 2013-08-11

# Mathematics E-Learning System, Singapore Math

ACE-Learning.com, **(referred to as "us" or "we" or "ACE-Learning.com" or "ACE-Learning Systems Pte. Ltd.")** , is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the ACE-Learning.com website located at [www.ace-learning.com](http://www.ace-learning.com/) **("Website")** , and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing such information. This Privacy Policy is part of the ACE-Learning.com Website _Terms of Use_ **(collectively, the "Website Policies")** , and you accept that by accessing or using the Website, you agree to be bound by all the terms of the Website Policies. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect: (i) on this Website, (ii) in text and electronic messages between you and this Website, and (iii) via mobile applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interactions between you and this Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by us offline or via third-party sites that may be accessed through hyperlinks on this Website. 

By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes. 

##  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE WEBSITE POLICIES, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEBSITE. 

Please read the information below:

  * Information we collect about you
  * Where we store data
  * How we use your information
  * Disclosure of your information
  * Updating or correcting your personally identifiable information
  * Cancelling your account or deleting your personally identifiable information
  * Choices regarding control of your personally identifiable information
  * Information related to data collected through the ACE-Learning.com platform service
  * Data security
  * Cookies
  * Mobile analytics
  * Links to third party web sites and advertisers
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Communities, forums, chat rooms, and message boards
  * Social media features
  * How do you contact us?

1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We collect several types of information about visitors to this Website and/or users of our services. We may collect this information either directly when you provide it to us or automatically as you navigate through the Website. 

(a) Personally Identifiable Information. "Personally Identifiable Information" refers to information by which you may be personally identified, such as your name, email address, or school. We will collect and process such data about you when you register for a service/create an account, subscribe to a newsletter, submit feedback, enter a contest, fill out a survey, or send us a communication. When ordering products or services on the Website, you may also be asked to provide a credit card number and other payment-related information. You may also provide information to be published or displayed ( **"posted"** ) on public areas of the Website (such as blogs, forums, message boards, and the like), or transmitted to other users of the Website using "sharing" features ( **collectively, "User Contributions"** ). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. We do not collect more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary for a child to participate in an activity on the Website. If you are a school and you use the ACE-Learning.com service for children under the age of 13, you are responsible for obtaining consent from the parents/legal guardians of each child you wish to allow to participate in using any ACE-Learning.com service. A child using the service will be able to participate in certain activities on the Website such as taking online educational and informational courses. 

(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information. We may collect, or our third party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information, that does not by itself identify a specific individual. Such information tells us about your equipment, browsing actions, the resources that you access and use on the Website, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, operating system and browser type. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Website and to gather demographic information. Our third party ad servers will provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our Website. The information that we collect automatically is "statistical" in nature. It helps us to deliver a better and more personalized service to users, by enabling us to estimate usage patterns, customize our Website according to your individual preferences, and speed up your searches. 

(c) Device Information. When you download our mobile application and use our services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and the operating system version, so we know the best application version to provide you with. We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our Mobile Application or services. 

2\. WHERE WE STORE DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination in Singapore. It may also be processed by staff operating outside Singapore who works for us or for one of our service providers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. ACE-Learning.com will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection
  * If you pay for a service using a credit card, we will transmit your credit card data to the appropriate credit card company and/or credit card payment processing company
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so
  * To notify you about changes to our service
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those, which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

If you use the Contact Us form on our site, we will respond to your inquiry and delete the information provided after your request has been fulfilled.

4\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell, trade, rent or disclose your information to others, except as provided herein: 

(a) We provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with services providers and other third parties. Our service partners and we use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our websites and to deliver services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on this Website; release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control.

(b) We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in the following circumstances:

  * If it is required by law enforcement or judicial authorities, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation; 
  * If we have a good faith belief that we are required or permitted to do so by law or legal process; 
  * To protect the rights, reputation, property or safety of ACE-Learning.com or others; 
  * To defend or enforce our rights or your obligations; 
  * If the disclosure is required by mandatory professional standards; 
  * To a 3rd party with your prior consent to do so; or 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to enforce or apply our Website Policies, or any contracts or agreement that may exist between you and ACE-Learning.com. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

(c) In the event that ACE-Learning.com decides to sell all or part of its stock or assets or enter into a merger, we reserve the right to include Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring or surviving company.

(d) We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related Website information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

(e) Parent's are able to consent to the use of their child's Personal Information without having to consent to the Website's disclosure of the child's Personal Information to third parties, as we do not share personal information of children under the age of 13 with any third parties (other than those service partners who help us provide the ACE-Learning.com service to you).

5\. UPDATING OR CORRECTING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

You may change any of yours or your child's Personally Identifiable Information online by logging into "ACE-Learning Account" in accordance with instructions posted elsewhere on this Website.

For Students, you may change your Personally Identifiable Information except your name and NRIC.

You may also access, request deletion, and correct yours or your child's personal information and privacy preferences by emailing us at support@acelearn.com or writing to us at: 

10 Ubi Crescent  
#06-95 Ubi Techpark  
Singapore 408564 

Please include yours or your child's name, address, and e-mail address when you contact us. We encourage you to promptly update yours or your child's Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on yours or your child's account deleted or removed and request that we no longer have contact with your child; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on this Website. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups.

6\. CANCELLING YOUR ACCOUNT OR DELETING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

If you are ACE-Learning.com subscriber and would like to cancel your membership, please contact your sales representatives or contact support@acelearn.com. To have any personally identifiable information deleted, please contact: support@acelearn.com. We will retain yours or your child's information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel yours or your child's account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@acelearn.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

7\. CHOICES REGARDING YOUR CONTROL OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

You can access some of the information that we collect about you or your child. For example, you can access information regarding recent orders from the Website; Personally Identifiable Information; communication preferences; and payment settings. 

With respect to your communications preferences, you can unsubscribe from newsletters by following the instructions included in the newsletter you receive or you can log into your account and update your newsletter and email subscription options. If your e-mail address has changed and you would like to continue to receive newsletters, you will need to access your account and update your e-mail address information in your account and sign-up again for the newsletter. Occasionally we may send out e-mails concerning website disruptions. 

If you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from our partners, and us we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only ACE-Learning.com (or agents working on behalf of us and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you did not "opt-out" of such offers. 

We do not send unsolicited commercial e-mails ("spam"), buy or sell e-mail lists, or use purchased or harvested e-mail lists. We offer commercial e-mail recipients the opportunity to opt-out of further communications in every email. Please note that we may not include the opt-out information in non-commercial e-mails (i.e., e-mails concerning your order, the Website Terms and Conditions of Use, etc.). 

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our Website may not work properly in your case. 

8\. INFORMATION RELATED TO DATA COLLECTED THROUGH THE  
ACE-LEARNING.COM PLATFORM SERVICE

For certain services ACE-Learning.com collects information under the direction of its clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. ACE-Learning.com works with its clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected. In these cases, ACE-Learning.com has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to the relevant ACE-Learning.com client (the data controller). If the client makes a request to us to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days. Similarly, if you are a customer of one of these clients and would no longer like to be contacted by that client, please contact that client directly. ACE-Learning.com may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Privacy Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our clients. 

ACE-Learning.com will retain personal data we process on behalf of our clients for as long as needed to provide services to our client. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

9\. DATA SECURITY

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. 

To make online purchases you must use an SSL-enabled browser in order to protect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet. 

Access by you to your account is available through a password and/or unique username selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone, that you change your password often using a combination of letters and numbers, and that you ensure you use a secure web browser. We cannot be held accountable for activity that results from your own neglect to safeguard the secrecy of your password and username. If you share a computer with anyone, you should always log out of the Website before leaving it to prevent access to your information from subsequent users of that computer. 

You should notify us promptly if your username or password is compromised. If you are suspicious of an inquiry for your account information, contact us immediately by telephone at (65) 6848 9320 or by email at support@acelearn.com. 

Personal information that you provide that is not Personally Identifiable Information also resides on a secure server and is only accessible via password. Since this information is not accessible from outside ACE-Learning.com, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Website cannot be guaranteed and we shall have no liability to you or any third party for loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration of such information; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. 

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personally Identifiable Information in our control may have been compromised, we will notify you as promptly as possible under the circumstances. To the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail and you consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at support@acelearn.com with the alternative contact information you wish to be used. 

10\. COOKIES

When you use our Website we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our Website.

**_What is a cookie?_** A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us.

Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our Website. The cookies make your use of the Website easier, make the Website run more smoothly, and save your logged-in state so that you do not have to log in each time that you visit the Website. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but if you do so, our Website will not recognize your computer and you may not have access to all portions of the Website.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers, is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers, use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

We partner with third party ad networks to manage our advertising on other sites. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any third-party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information or information about your purchases. We and our third party ad server will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular advertisement. 

11\. MOBILE ANALYTICS

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application. 

12\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES AND ADVERTISERS

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Our Website may contain hyperlinks to other third-party web sites, which may collect and disclose information in a manner that is different from our Website. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these third-party web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of the other web sites. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our Website may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

13\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page (with a notice that the Privacy Policy has been updated on the Website home page). If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and through a notice on the Website home page. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes. 

Your continued use of the Website after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make material changes to how we use Personal Information collected from Children under 13, we will notify parents by email in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of their child’s personally identifiable information. 

15\. COMMUNITIES, FORUMS, CHAT ROOMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS

If you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information on communities, message boards, forums, and the like, which may be accessible via this Website, you should be aware that such information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@acelearn.com. You acknowledge and accept that any submissions to chat rooms or other public areas on this Website are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for all activity conducted by you via communities, forums, message boards, chat rooms, etc. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

16\. SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as Widgets, such as the Add this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Website. This feature may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

17\. HOW DO YOU CONTACT US WITH QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us by sending a letter to: 

10 Ubi Crescent  
#06-95 Ubi Techpark  
Singapore 408564

Tel:(65) 6848 9320  
Fax:(65) 6848 9321

You may also contact us by e-mail at support@acelearn.com
